

Nguyen Tran

Consultant at TMA Solutions - TMA Innovation Center

Connect

♠ Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

△ Message

• • •

Nguyen Tran · 3rd

Consultant at TMA Solutions - TMA Innovation Center

Vietnam · 104 connections · Contact info



TMA Solutions



National Chung Cheng University

People and pages related to Nguyen

See all



>





Follow



Ryan Roslansky CEO at LinkedIn 373,465 followers

Follow



Doug McMillon inPresident & CEO at Walmart Inc.
859,225 followers

Follow

About

Experienced in Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Deep Learning, Machine Learning, C#, Matlab, and C (Programming Language). Strong consulting professional with a Master's degree focused on AI, Computer vision from National Chung Cheng University.

Activity

104 followers

Posts Nguyen created, shared, or commented on in the last 90 days are displayed here.

See all activity

Experience

Senior Al Developer

TMA Solutions · Full-time

Var 2019 – Present

· 2 yrs 2 mos

Vietnam

Be in charge of AI, machine learning, deep learning focus on Image, NLP Projects:

- E-commerce project: Text generation, Paraphrasing, Named Entity Recognition, Sentiment Analysis.
- Call Center Analysis: Named Entity Recognition, Sentiment Analysis.
- Machine optimization: Reinforcement learning.
- Car parking monitoring: Vehicle recognition, Licence plate recognition.
- Vietnamese text to speech model
- ID card OCR ... see more

Masters Student

National Chung Cheng University
-eb 2017 – Jan 2019

· 2 yrs

Chiayi County/City, Taiwan

Research topic: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Image processing, Computer vision

Thesis: Deep learning approach for Indoor Localization based on Wi-Fi signal

Senior Software Engineer

Robert Bosch Engineering and Business Solutions Vietnam

Oct 2013 – Feb 2017

возсн ⋅ 3 yrs 5 mos
 з yrs 5 mos
 возсн ⋅ 3 yrs 5 mos
 возс

364 Cong Hoa, Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City

Be in charge of Embedded Software Engineer for Powertrain System (Driver Assistance, Vehicle Motion, Vehicle Device ...)

- Working with Matlab, C
- 3 months working in Bosch Bangalore, India

Graduate Student

Ho Chi Minh University of Technical Education

May 2010 – Jul 2013

· 3 yrs 3 mos

Vietnam

Automotive Technology, mainly focuses on automotive electronics and programming.

Education

National Chung Cheng University

Vaster's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering 2017 – 2019

Ho Chi Minh University of Technical Education

Licenses & certifications

Self-Service Data Preparation in SAS® Viya®



Skills & endorsements

Deep Learning

Machine Learning . 1

Trung-Hieu Nguyen has given an endorsement for this skill

Programming . 1

Trung-Hieu Nguyen has given an endorsement for this skill

Tools & Technologies

Matlab . 1

C . 1

C# . 1

Show less ^

Interests

Robert Bosch Engineering and Business Solutions Vietnam



National Chung Cheng University 13,496 followers



Bosch



TMA Solutions

5,811 followers



People also viewed



蘇愷 •3rd+

國立中正大學學生

Connect



沈哲墉 •3rd+

國立中央大學學生

Connect

蔡承諭 •3rd+

學生 - 交通大學

Connect



You-Chen Lin •3rd+

Student at National Taiwan University (NTU)

Connect



Bach Luong •3rd

Senior Software Engineer at Tamtay.vn

Connect

∨Show more

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

Student at Ton Duc Thang University

Connect

∨Show more



Add new skills with these courses



Introduction to Deep Learning with OpenCV

18,355 viewers



Reinforcement Learning Foundations

1,534 viewers



Applied Machine Learning: Algorithms

49,688 viewers

Show more on LinkedIn Learning





LinkedIn Corporation © 2021







Search messages After April 15, 2021, your read receipts and typing indicators setting will expand to all messages, including InMails and Message Requests.

Manage settings Got it